但我没有
but that's not what I did.
写媒体  写纽约精英
Writing about the media, writing about the New York elite,
写人们能与之产生共鸣的故事
telling personal stories that resonate with readers
根本不会影响对叙利亚
doesn't take one cent away from covering Syria
阿富汗或者华盛顿的报道
and Afghanistan and Washington.
我们有驻外记者
There are foreign correspondents,
也有体育记者和时尚记者
sports correspondents, fashion correspondents.
还有让人忍无可忍
And an unbearable correspondent.
嫉妒纽约精英的记者  我说全了吧
Jealous of the New York elites? I've got you covered.
某影星参加环保筹款会
A movie star was at an environmental fundraiser
但他们却开私人飞机
and they rode on a private jet?
听听你虚假的愤怒吧
Here's your phony outrage.
你觉得自己不够好
Feeling a little like you didn't make the cut?
我在此宣布业余记者碉堡了
I hereby declare that amateurs are awesome